Inventaris van het archief van mr. D.U. Stikker [levensjaren 1897-1979], 1938-1979
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- Overige stukken., IV
  - Place of Private Enterprise., II
    - UNCTAD Report; A: Uitnodiging Report, Correspondentie over eventuele aanvaarding opdracht., 1966; 204; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; B: Correspondentie Prebisch., 1966-1968; 205; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; C: Correspondentie Assistenten Prebisch, Müller, Greenhill, Viteri de la Huerta, Krishnamurti., 1966; 206; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; D: Correspondentie P. Hoffman (UNDP)., 1967; 207; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; E: Correspondentie UNCTAD Financiën., 1967-1968; 208; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; F: Correspondentie Ford Foundation., 1966-1968; 209; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; G: Correspondentie McCargar., 1966-1967; 210; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; H: Veranderingen, J.S. Raj MRS, Boskey, Prebisch and Staff., 1967; 211; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; I: Questionnaires, Draft outlines., 1966-1967; 212; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; J: Toestemming overdruk Chapter IV, Toestemming Duitse vertaling., 1968; 213; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; K: Reacties toezending Report, dankbetuigingen., 1967-1968; 214; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; L: Correspondentie over druk Report met Berthoud, Graham; Afscheid Prebisch en eventuele opvolging., 1967-1968; 215; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; M: UNCTAD II New Delhi., 1968; 216; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; N: Reacties van derden over Report; Farbstein, Smets, Bailey, Bloembergen e.a., 1967-1968; 217; 9
    - UNCTAD Report; O: Artikelen en speeches van derden over ontwikkelingshulp algemeen, Baudet, 't Hooft-Welvaars, Rosenstein-Rodan, Meagher e.a., 1967-1968; 218; 9
    - United Nations Institute for Training and Research (UNITAR)., 1968-1969; 219; 9
    - United Nations Industrial Development Organization (UNIDO)., 1967-1970; 220; 9
    - United Nations Development Program (UNDP)., 1967-1969; 221; 9
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Bank for Reconstruction and Development/ International Development Association., 1965-1968; 222; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Bank for Reconstruction and Development/ International Finance Corporation., 1963-1966; 223; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Commonwealth Development Corporation., 1968-1970; 224; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; IBRD/ Correspondence., 1966-1967; 225; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Centre for Settlement of Investment Disputes., 1965, 1967; 226; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Overseas Development Council (US)., 1968; 227; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Deutsche Entwicklungs Gesellschaft., 1968-1969; 228; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Committee for Economic Development, Latin America., 1965-1967; 229; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Committee for Economic Development, Mediteranean., 1965; 230; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Committee for Economic Development, Far East., 1965, 1970; 231; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Chamber of Commerce, Correspondentie., 1966, 1968; 232; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Chamber of Commerce, Congress Karachi (1960), Copenhagen (1961), New Delhi (1965), Montreal (1967), Istanbul (1969)., 1960-1969; 233; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Chamber of Commerce, Publications., 1966-1969; 234; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Chamber of Commerce, Consultative Committee., 1968-1970; 235; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; B.I.A.C.: Cameroun, Turkey, Colombia., 1966-1969; 236; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; National Industrial Conference Board., 1966-1970; 237; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Industrial Conference Board., 238; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Industrial Conference/Stanford Research Institute., 1969; 239; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investment (APPI/WOODS)., 1966-1967; 240; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; International Association for the Promotion and Protection of Private Foreign Investment (APP1/UNCTAD)., 1965-1966; 241; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Agency for International Development (AID)., 1966-1967; 242; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Confederation of British Industry., 1969; 243; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Overseas Development Institution., 1967-1968; 244; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Nederlandse Financierings Maatschappij voor Ontwikkelingslanden., 1969; 245; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Nationale Raad van Advies inzake Hulpverlening aan Minder-Ontwikkelde Landen., 1968-1969; 246; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Society for International Development., 1969; 247; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Business Council for International Understanding (BCIU)., 1966-1967; 248; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Organization of American States/Business Advisory Council., 1967; 249; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; Shell Special Studies., 1964-1967; 250; 10
    - Investment Promotion and Institutions; UN Economic Commission for Africa., 1966-1967; 251; 10
  - Legal Aspects., III
    - Correspondence with Blair, Sandberg, Lindgren., 1966-1967; 252
    - Philosophy, Sovereignty Political Risks, Rules of Law, Recommandations, Human Rights., 1966-1968; 253; 1
    - Investment Promotion Legislation., 1966-1968; 254; 2
    - Multilateral and Bilateral Measures (Treaties)., 1967-1970; 255; 3
    - Arbitration and Conciliation., 1965-1966; 256; 4
    - Insurance, Multilateral., 1966-1968; 257; 5
    - Insurance., 1965-1969; 258; 5
    - Industrial Property and Patent Law., 1965-1970; 259; 6
    - Restrictive Business Practices., 1969; 260; 7
  - Taxation., IV
    - Taxation General., 1966-1970; 261
    - Correspondence about Chapter IV, Report Taxation Aspects., 1967-1970; 262
  - Government Policies (DCs) and Private Investment., V
    - Public and Private Sector: Planning and DCs., 1966-1969; 263; 1
  - Visits to Developing Countries., VI
    - Latin America, General, Bohan Report., 1966-1969; 264; 1
    - Latin America, Brazil, General., 1964-1969; 265; 1
    - Latin America, Brazil, Krantenknipsels., 1966-1967; 266; 1
    - Latin America, Brazil, Personal visit., 1967; 267; 1
    - Latin America, Colombia., 1964; 268; 1
    - Latin America, Peru., 1965-1967; 269; 1
    - Latin America, Peru, Conflict International Petroleum Company-Peru., 1968; 270; 1
    - Latin America, Suriname., 1968; 271; 1
    - Latin America, Venezuela., 1961-1967; 272; 1
    - Asia-India I, Documentatie en Prospecti., 1964-1968; 273; 2
    - Asia-India II, Verslag van bezoeken, adressen, krantenartikelen., 1967; 274; 2
    - Asia-India III, General., 1964-1968; 275; 2
    - Asia-India, Fertilizers., 1965-1969; 276; 2
    - Asia-Pakistan I, General, visit adressen., 1965-1966; 277; 2
    - Asia-Pakistan II, verslag van bezoeken, tijdschriften, krantenknipsels., 1967; 278; 2
    - Africa, General., 1965-1969; 279; 3
    - East-Africa, General., 1965-1967; 280; 3
    - Africa, Ghana., 1967; 281; 3
    - Africa, Ivory Coast., 1965-1967; 282; 3
    - Africa, Kenya., 1965-1967; 283; 3
    - Africa, Tanzania., 1966-1967; 284; 3
    - Africa, Uganda., 1964-1967; 285; 3
    - Europe, Vatican., 1967; 286; 4
  - Exports of Manufactures and Semi-Manufactures by DCs., VII
    - Commodities, General., 1965-1969; 287; 1
    - Commodities and Commodities Agreements; Cocoa, Rubber, Coffee, Rice, Tea, Tobacco, Textiles., 1965-1970; 288; 2
    - Barriers to export; Trade Policies-EEC, Tariff Barriers ICs, Non-Tariff Barriers (N.T.B.)., 1966-1969; 289; 3
  - Promotion of Exports., VIII
    - Trade policies of ICs; Kennedy Round., 1966-1967; 290; 1
    - Trade policies of ICs; GATT., 1962-1968; 291; 1
    - Trade policies of ICs; Common Market., 1967-1969; 292; 1
    - Commercial Politics., 1965-1967; 293; 2
    - Regional Integration., 1965-1969; 294; 3
  - Panel on Foreign Investment in Developing Countries, Amsterdam., IX
    - Documenten UN and ECOSOC about Panel, Voorbereiding., 1968; 295; 1
    - Correspondentie met: Blair, Haight, Bailey, Hoffman, Lachman e.a., Voorbereiding., 1967-1969; 296; 2
    - Correspondentie met minister Udink, Statement Kaufmann, Voorbereiding., 1968-1969; 297; 3
    - Suggesties van Ramaer voor Panel, Voorbereiding., 1967-1969; 298; 4
    - Draft for Panel Documents., 1968-1969; 299; 5
    - Panel zelf, Opening door minister Udink., 1968-1969; 300; 6
    - Panel zelf, Officiële Papieren., 1969; 301; 7
    - Pers over Panel., 1969; 302; 8
    - Artikelen over Panel of verwijzingen naar Panel in speeches of rapporten., 1969; 303; 9
    - Final Report., 1969; 304; 10
  - Radio Free Europe., IX A
    Zie ook lijstnrs. 115 en 149-153
    - 12th and 13th Session Western European Advisory Committee., 1968-1969; 305
    - Bezoeken aan New York en München., 1970; 306
    - 14th Session Western European Advisory Committee., 1970; 307
    - Bijeenkomst Western European Advisory Committee., 1972; 308
    - Correspondentie met Schiff, Van Campen, Brosio, articles from newspapers, address by Elliot Richardson., 1970; 309
    - Country Studies., 1969-1970; 310
    - Research., 1969-1970; 311
    - Communist Nations, East-European and Anti-R.F.E. campaign, Audience Mail., 1969-1970; 312
    - Correspondence Meeting New York, Press reactions., 1971; 313
  - Panel on Foreign Investment in Latin America, Medellin., X
    - Working Papers, UN Documents., 1969-1970; 314; 1
    - Participants., 1970; 315; 2
    - Preparation Paper, UN Documents, Major Issues For Discussion., 1970; 316; 3
    - Preparation Paper, UN Documents., 1969-1970; 317; 4
    - Correspondence R.J. Blair, Philippe de Seynes., 1969-1970; 318; 5
    - Correspondence., 1969-1970; 319; 5
    - Background Documents, UN Documents., 1969-1970; 320; 6
    - Background Documents, CIA (Center for Inter-American Relations) Documents., 1968-1970; 321; 7
    - Background Documents, ICC (International Chamber of Commerce) Documents., 1969-1970; 322; 8
    - Background Documents, OAS (Organization of American States Documents, IA-ECOSOC (Inter-American Economic and Social Council)., 1966-1967; 323; 9
    - Background Documents, OAS (Organization of American States Documents, IA-ECOSOC (Inter-American Economic and Social Council)., 1969-1970; 324; 9
    - Background Documents, BIAC (Business and Industry Advisory Committee to OECD)., 1969-1970; 325; 10
    - Background Documents, OECD (Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development)., 1968-1970; 326; 11
    - Background Documents, NFTC (National Foreign Trade Council Inc.) Documents., 1969; 327; 12
    - Background Documents, Individuals., 1969-1970; 328; 13
    - Background Documents, Organizations., 1969; 329; 14
    - Background Documents, Magazine and Newspaper Articles., 1969-1970; 330; 15
    - Panel Meeting Documents., 1970; 331; 16
    - Panel Meeting Documents., 1969-1970; 332; 16
    - Congresmap., 1970; 333
    - Panel Meeting Results., 1970; 334; 17
    - Round Table Rome., 1970-1971; 335; 18
    - Stukken betreffende de samenstelling van zijn aan de secretaris-generaal van de UNCTAD uitgebrachte rapport The role of private enterprise in investment of export in developing countries., 1966-1967; 336-347
      Zie lijstnrs. 204-218
      - Correspondence on Draft Chapters., 336
      - Acknowledgements, Preface and Contents., 337
      - Chapter I., 338
      - Chapter II., 339
      - Chapter III., 340
      - Chapter IV., 341
      - Chapter V., 342
      - Chapter VI., 343
      - Chapter VII., 344
      - Chapter VIII., 345
      - Chapter IX., 346
      - Chapter X., 347
    - Kaartsysteem op de rubrieken I - XI., 348-350
      - Rubrieken I - II., 348
      - Rubrieken III - IX., 349
      - Rubrieken X - XI., 350